<resources>
    <string name="app_name">hillside</string>
    <string name="about_us">
        Hillside primary school is a private mixed Day and Boarding registered with the Ministry of Education and Sports. It is a Non – denominational school which strives for Academic Excellence, Discipline and Spirituality.

Hillside provides a holistic Curriculum to cater for the learners’ proper growth and development needs.

Since its inception in 2001, the school has registered remarkable growth and development in terms of infrastructure and population. The school now has semi autonomous Nursery Section with a spacious environment for the pupils various activities.
    </string>
    <string name="nursery">We are dedicated to providing a child-centered environment. Our early childhood care and education centers provide quality long day care, before, after school care and vacation care for children birth to 6 years.</string>
    <string name="results">Teachers will explain these rules to their classes annually and display the rules in the Classroom. Pupils enter the school on the understanding that they know and will obey these rules.   Parents are expected to give their co-operation and support in the enforcement of the rules and of discipline in general.

School Property, Personal Property and the Property of Others
1. Pupils are expected to keep the school buildings and grounds free of litter.

2. The chewing of gum is forbidden in school.

3. To assist the cleaners, chairs must be turned upside down and put on tables at the end of the day.

4. Damage to school property should be reported to the class teacher.  Repair of damage and removal of graffiti must be paid for by the perpetrator.

5. Pupils are expected to take good care of their textbooks and to return them to their teachers at the end of the year.  Pupils who fail to do so will be required to compensate the school.

Behavior and Good Manners
Safety and Security
Uniform and Personal Appearance\n As of these rules we were able to attain these:\n Hillside Primary School Naalya is among the very best primary schools in Uganda and this below is proof of the school’s continued excellence, the school’s performance over the last 5 years.</string>
</resources>